we're all tempted with anger on the
我们都被愤怒的诱惑所吸引
highway right in the LA area this
这是洛杉矶地区的高速公路
morning as I was driving down here I had
早上我在这里开车时，我有
this big black pickup truck weaving in
这个大黑色皮卡车编织而成
and out of traffic just zooming by
进出交通的只是飞驰而过
everybody and I thought while dude it's
每个人和我都在想，而这个人
Saturday morning just relax we can't we
星期六早上放松我们不能
even relaxed in the traffic on Saturday
周六的交通甚至放松了
morning in the LA area recently and the
早上在洛杉矶地区最近和
reason I'm starting with the traffic
原因我开始与交通
illustration is because recently some
插图是因为最近有些
research has been done on what's called
所谓的研究已经完成
intermittent explosive disorder that's
间歇性爆发性疾病
the dsm-4 category and let me read to
dsm-4类别让我读一读
you some research now this came out a
你现在进行了 一些研究，结果出来了
few years ago out of Chicago to you that
几年前从芝加哥出来的那个
angry horn blasting tailgater is
愤怒的角爆破尾门是
suffering from road rage but doctors
道路愤怒，但医生
have another name for it intermittent
有间歇性的另一个名字
explosive disorder it affects up to 16
爆发性疾病最多可影响16人
million Americans dr. Emil Kokoro from
百万美国人博士。 EmilKokoro来自
the University of Chicago's Medical
芝加哥大学医学院
School said quote people think it's bad
学校说引用人们认为这很糟糕
behavior and that you need an attitude
行为， 你需要一个态度
adjustment but what they don't know is
调整，但他们不知道的是
that there's a biology and cognitive
有生物学和认知
science to this another researcher said
科学对另一位研究人员说
it's news to a lot of people even who
这对许多人来说都是新闻， 甚至是谁
are specialists in mental health
是心理健康方面的专家
services that such a large proportion of
服务这么大的比例
the population has these clinically
人口在临床上有这些
significant anger attacks remember the
重大的愤怒攻击记得
statistic that I read 16 million is the
统计，我读1600万 是
number that is being attached to this
正在附加的数字
now here's some world view statements I
现在这里有一些世界观的陈述我
spoke the last time about looking at
谈到最后一次地看着
people and their problems through the
人们和他们的问题通过
lenses of your presuppositions of what
对你的预设的镜头
do you believe about humans etc here's
你相信关于人类等这里的
what dr. kokoro said and you're gonna
什么博士kokoro说，你会的
hear some worldview type of assumptions
听一些世界观的假设
here
这里
he said the disorder involves inadequate
他说这种疾病涉及不足
production or
生产或
functioning of serotonin a mood
血清素的功能是一种情绪
regulating and behavior inhibiting brain
调节和行为抑制大脑
chemical treatment with antidepressants
用抗抑郁药进行化学治疗
including those that target serotonin
包括那些靶向血清素的人
receptors in the brain is often helpful
大脑中的受体通常很有帮助
along with behavior therapy akin to
随着行为疗法类似于
anger management now what I would like
愤怒管理现在我想要什么
to propose as we get into what the
提出为我们进入什么
scriptures say about what's going on as
圣经说一下这是怎么回事作为
we look at all of the different labels
我们看所有的不同标签
that the world might associate with
世界可能会联想到
anger type of problems and there's many
愤怒类型的问题，有很多
many more in the DSM 4 is that our God
更多在DSM4是我们的上帝
as the creator of humans understands
正如人类的创造者所理解的那样
chemicals in the brain better than
大脑中的化学物质比
anyone and he had some opinions as the
任何人和他都有一些意见
writer ultimate writer of Scripture
圣经的作家最终作家
because we believe scriptures the
因为我们相信经文
inspired inerrant Word of God God has
神神的灵感无误的Word有
some opinions about anger and what's
关于愤怒和什么的 一些看法
going on and it does raise some really
继续，它确实提高了一些
interesting questions of what do we do
关于我们做什么的有趣问题
with all of the current research etc and
与所有目前的研究等 ，并
when I speak this afternoon on physical
当我在物理 今天下午发言
illness and biblical counseling we're
我们是疾病和圣经咨询
gonna talk a little bit more about that
再谈谈这个问题
but a wonderful book has been written
但是写了一本很棒的书
that try to a that tries to address from
尝试尝试解决的问题
a biblical perspective what do we do
从圣经的角度来看，我们做了什么
with all the brain research and it's
所有的大脑研究和它的
from a biblical counseling perspective
从圣经的咨询角度来看
it's called blame it on the brain by dr.
它被称为责备大脑由博士。
Edie Welch and Edie Welch is a
伊迪韦尔奇和伊迪韦尔奇是一个
neuropsychologist his PhD is in neuro
神经心理学家，他的博士学位是神经病学
psychology but his m.div is in biblical
心理学，但他的m.div是符合圣经的
counseling so he's a kind of a rare
咨询所以他是一种罕见的
combination in the biblical counseling
在圣经辅导中的组合
world and what he's trying to do in that
世界和他正在努力做的事情
book is wrestle with well what do we do
我们正在努力争取书籍
with all the brain research and it would
所有的大脑研究，它会
be very helpful for you to read that
非常有帮助你阅读
book sometime because I can guarantee to
预订， 因为我可以保证
you with angry people if they've been
你是愤怒的人，如果他们曾经
through counseling before they're gonna
通过咨询之前他们会
come to you with brain theories as to
用大脑理论来找你
why they do the things that they do
为什么他们做他们做的事情
listen to what God's Word says here's
听听上帝的话在这里说的话
the creator of the universe writing
宇宙写作的创造者
about anger and he says through the
关于愤怒，他说通过
psalmist
诗人
cease from anger and forsake wrath do
停止愤怒和放弃愤怒
not fret it leads only to evil doing boy
不要担心它只会导致邪恶的男孩
don't we know that from our counseling
我们从咨询中得知这一点
anger leading to evil doing holes and
愤怒导致邪恶做洞和
walls
墙壁
wrecked vehicles hurt people that have
失事车辆伤害具有人
been punched etc proverbs 14 9 he is
被殴打等谚语14 9他是
slow to anger here's another thing the
这是另一回事
creator said he who is slow to anger has
创造者说，他的愤怒缓慢了
great understanding but he who is
很了解， 但他是谁
quick-tempered exalts folly so how do we
脾气暴躁的高举愚蠢所以我们怎么样
get to the place of being slow to anger
到了愤怒缓慢的地方
we address this a little bit the last
我们最后解决了这个问题
time and we're gonna address it even
时间，我们甚至会解决它
more what's going on in the soul
更多灵魂正在发生的事情
possibly of an angry person now let me
可能是一个愤怒的人现在让我
give you a definition of anger in this
给你一个愤怒的定义
definition comes out of I think the best
定义来自我认为最好的
book on anger from a biblical
预订圣经中的愤怒
perspective called uprooting anger
被称为根除愤怒的观点
biblical help for a common problem by
通过一个共同的问题圣经帮助
our friend dr. Robert Jones and he gives
我们的朋友博士罗伯特琼斯和他给
this definition he teaches at
他教导的这个定义
Southeastern Seminary he was a pastor
东南神学院他是牧师
for many years he says that anger is our
多年来 ，他说，愤怒是我们的
whole person and he's trying to address
整个人，他正试图解决
what our culture says anger is versus
我们的文化说愤怒是什么
what does the Bible say anger is our
圣经说什么愤怒是我们的
anger is our whole person active
愤怒是我们整个人的活跃
response of negative moral judgment
否定道德判断的反应
against perceived evil doesn't take long
反对感知邪恶并不需要很长时间
thinking through that you realize he's
想通过你意识到他是
saying there's not just something going
说这不仅仅是一件事
on in your brain there's something going
在你的大脑中有一些事情发生
on deeper in your soul you are making
在你的灵魂深处，你正在制造
judgments about another person and what
关于另一个人的判断和什么
that person what you perceive your
那个人你认为你的
perceptions of what you perceive that
的看法您认为是什么
person has done and we're gonna get into
人已经完成了，我们将要进入
this in just a little while but doesn't
这只是一段时间但不是
that start getting into what I believe
开始进入我的信念
my rights are and just kind of start
我的权利只是一种开始
tucking away these type of think this
隐藏这些类型的想法
type of thinking for later in the
以后的思维 类型
presentation of really going through
介绍真正经历
with the angry person or with yourself
与愤怒的人或与你自己
if you are that person what are my
如果你是那个人我的是什么
perceived rights and as a believer how
感知权利和信徒如何
do I think about my
我想到我的
right sir how should I think about my
对，先生，我该怎么想我的
rights and I'm gonna put a whole bunch
权利， 我要放一大堆
of things up on the screen as things
事物在屏幕上的东西
that we often as humans can want to hang
我们经常像人类一样想要挂起
on to and perceive as our rights and how
我们的权利和方式
should we think about rights from a
我们应该考虑一下权利吗？
biblical perspective let's go down
圣经的观点让我们走下坡路
through this definition just pretty
通过这个定义很漂亮
quickly whole person your mind your
很快你整个人的思想
emotions your will are involved it's a
感情你的意志是一个
whole person response that's what our
整个人的反应就是我们的
world our culture would call your
世界我们的文化会称呼你的
personality your mind and the way you
个性你的思想和你的方式
express your emotions and the way you
表达你的情绪和你的方式
make decisions it's whole person mind
做出决定是整个人的心灵
emotions and will it's an active
情绪， 它会是一个活跃的
response as we're about to see in just a
响应，我们在短短一看
few moments it's not just external it
没有什么时候它不仅仅是外部的
can be internal there can be things like
可以是内部可以有类似的东西
seething or maybe we use the polite word
沸腾或者我们使用礼貌的词
and we say I'm frustrated but seething
而且我们说我很沮丧但是沸腾了
being irritated all of those types of
所有这些类型的人都被激怒了
things can be going on on the inside as
事情可以 在里面为 来怎么回事
part of of anger some people it's more
愤怒的一部分，有些人更多
external some people anger is more
外部有些人的愤怒更多
something that is going on on the inside
这是怎么回事 就在里面的东西
negative moral judgment we are making
我们正在做出消极的道德判断
decisions
决定
it's what Robert Jones argues in his
这就是罗伯特琼斯在他的辩护中所说的
book is that it's arising from a
本书是由它产生的
judicial sense that we have I am making
司法意识我们正在制造
a decision that and I believe that you
一个决定，我相信你
sinned against me in some way or you're
以某种方式对我犯了罪，或者你是
not doing something that I believe that
不这样做 ，我相信的 东西
you should be doing or you're doing
你应该做或者你正在做
something that I don't want you to do
的东西，我不希望你做
and we make moral judgments against
我们做出道德判断
others against perceived evil and there
其他人反对感知邪恶和那里
it gets into personal perception it has
它进入了个人认知
to do with what I perceive and just
与我所感知和公正的事情有关
think about this for a moment the things
想一想这件事情
that get you angry may not be the things
让你生气可能不是事情
that get me angry so then from a for a
这让我生气，然后从一个
biblical counselor the question would be
圣经辅导员的问题是
what what just kind of screams out at me
什么只是对我尖叫
there would be well why do those things
那些东西会很好
get you angry you know not everything
让你生气你不知道一切
that causes and any of the emotions we
这会引起我们的任何情绪
could ask those types of questions
可以问这些类型的问题
is why are you fearful I may not be
你为什么害怕我可能不是
fearful about the things you're fearful
害怕你害怕的事情
about why does this thing stir your
为什么这个东西会搅动你的
anger it doesn't stir my anger and
愤怒，它不会激起我的愤怒和
pretty quickly you get into what's going
很快你就会进入正在发生的事情
on in the heart what's going on in that
在心里发生了什么
person's heart with your particular mind
人的心与你的特殊心灵
emotions and will let's go on and just
情绪，将让我们去和公正
think about for a moment the idea of
想一想这个想法
righteous anger and I'm not gonna spend
正义的愤怒，我不会花
a lot of time on this and a lot of
在这个有很多的时间和大量的
people like to argue let's well I don't
人们喜欢争辩说我很好
need to go to the passage because I have
需要去通道，因为我有
one of the main verses up here mark
标志之一的主要经文之一
chapter 11 and just think about this for
第11章，只是想想这对
a moment this is the famous passage that
片刻，这是着名的段落
folks go to for righteous anger and I'll
人们为了正义的愤怒而去，我会
just tell you right from the beginning I
从一开始就告诉你我
believe theoretically it is possible to
理论上相信它是可能的
have righteous anger but the more I
有正义的愤怒， 但我越多
understand my heart and its motives its
理解我的心和它的动机吧
drives and its desires the less I trust
驱动器和它的欲望越少我信任
myself so you can take that or leave
我自己也可以接受或离开
that whatever you want to do with it but
无论你想做什么， 但是
very commonly I have people and I'm sure
非常普遍我有人，我很有信心
you will have people or already have
你会有人或已经拥有
people justify their anger with
人们为他们的愤怒辩护
righteous anger and I would just urge
正义的愤怒，我只会敦促
you to continue to study what does the
你继续研究什么的
Bible have to say about the heart with
圣经不得不说出与之相关的内心
its thought Hebrews chapter 4 talks
它的思想是希伯来书第4章的谈话
about the thoughts and intentions of the
关于这个的想法和意图
heart and I think pretty quickly you'll
心里，我想你很快就会
get to the place of saying hmm I'm not
到了说嗯我不是的地方
sure I trust my inner person with its
我确信我相信我内心的人
thoughts and its intentions I'm not
思想和意图我不是
Jesus so he entered the temple and began
耶稣让他进入圣殿并开始了
to cast out those who were buying and
赶走那些正在购买和购买的人
selling in the temple and overturned the
在庙里卖，推翻了
tables of the moneychangers and the
货币兑换商和货币兑换表
seats of those selling doves and we know
我们知道那些卖鸽子的座位
he did that without sin could we do that
他这样做，没有罪，我们能做到这一点
without sin and I'm not sure that my
没有罪，我不确定我的
motives would be totally pure on the
动机完全是纯粹的
inside you can study that more on your
你可以在里面学习更多关于你的知识
own Robert Jones has a great section in
自己的罗伯特琼斯有一个伟大的部分
his book on that what I want to focus on
他关于我想要关注的那本书
obviously is unrighteous anger and what
显然是不正义的愤怒和什么
do we do with unrighteous anger because
我们是因为不正当的愤怒而做的
that really is the common
这真的很常见
problem whether it is external or
无论是外部还是外部问题
internal what do we do with that and
内部我们做什么与和
where is it coming from
它来自哪里
so let's think about external anger or
所以让我们考虑外部的愤怒或
vented anger for a moment proverbs 29 11
发泄愤怒片刻谚语29 11
says a full always loses his temper but
说满满的总是发脾气但是
a wise man holds it back proverbs 19:11
一个聪明人持有它回到箴言19:11
urges us to be the type of person that
敦促我们成为那种人
learns how to overlook a transgression
学会如何忽视违规行为
that ties right back into the last
紧紧联系到最后
presentation about learning those
关于学习这些的介绍
character traits from Ephesians chapter
以弗所书章中的人物特征
4 as the Lord is working on me from the
4因为耶和华正在为我工​​作
inside out that I learned to be a person
从里到外我学会了成为一个人
that knows how to overlook
知道如何忽视
transgressions let me ask you a question
违法让我问你一个问题
I heard Jay Adams say this a long time
我听说杰伊·亚当斯说，这是一个很长一段时间
ago and it's just stuck with me for
以前，它只是坚持我
years and that is are you a person that
年，那是你的一个人
has big toes are you a person that your
有大脚趾你是一个人，你
toes are stepped on regularly and it
脚趾经常踩到它
just seems like you're easily offended
看起来你很容易受到冒犯
you're easily hurt then ask yourself the
你很容易受伤然后问问自己
question why do I have such big toes why
问为什么我有这么大的脚趾为什么
is it that I'm just so easily hurt and
是不是我很容易受伤？
we'll and just kind of keep that tucked
我们只是保持那种隐藏
away in your mind as we go through this
当我们经历这个时 ，你会想到这一点
presentation of where could anger be
介绍愤怒的地方
becoming from and just saying lord help
变得来自并且只是说主帮助
me not to be so sensitive
我不要那么敏感
shouldn't it be let's just speculate
不应该让它只是推测
here for a moment shouldn't it be that
这一刻不应该那样
as we are growing in our relationship
因为我们在关系中成长
with the Lord
与 主 同在
and the gospel is permeating our hearts
和福音 的渗透我们的心
more and more you're becoming think of
你越来越想到了
some key words that relate to the gospel
一些与福音有关的关键词
here's some key words that relate to the
这里，涉及到的一些关键词
gospel grace mercy peace joy forgiveness
福音恩惠怜悯和平快乐宽恕
ken sandy one of my favorite authors he
ken sandy是我最喜欢的作家之一
wrote a book called the peacemaker one
写了一本叫做调解人的书
of his famous statements is if
他的着名陈述是否如果
Christians are the most forgiving people
基督徒是最宽容的人
in the world shouldn't we be the most
在世界上我们不应该是最多的
forgiving people in the world so let's
宽恕世界上的人们，让我们这样做吧
speculate if the gospel is permeating my
推测福音是否渗透到了我的心中
soul and I'm growing in Christ's
灵魂，我在基督里成长
likeness
像
shouldn't I be a person whose
我不应该是一个人
hoes are shrinking I'm becoming more
锄头正在缩小我变得越来越多
merciful I'm becoming more gracious I'm
仁慈的我变得更加亲切，我
becoming more long-suffering the older I
变得更长久以来我受苦了
get it should be the the harder it
得到它应该是越难
should be to offend me as a person
应该冒犯我作为一个人
because I'm growing in in all of the
因为我在所有的在成长
things that are related to the gospel
这都涉及到福音事
vented anger versus the slow burn let's
发泄愤怒与缓慢燃烧让我们
compare those two things outward versus
向外与比较这两件事情
internal so external versus internal
内部如此外部与内部
obviously yelling screaming slamming
显然大喊大叫砰的一声
things cursing telling someone a piece
诅咒某人的事情
of your mind
你的思想
I had a counseling session a few years
我有一个咨询会议在几年
ago a woman was on her third marriage
一个女人在第三次婚姻
she had she approached her third
她让她接近她的第三个
marriage she talked about being set up
她谈到建立婚姻
for problems she approached her third
因为问题，她接近了她的第三个
marriage with this mentality men are
与男人结婚这种心态
stupid they're gonna try to take
愚蠢他们会尝试采取
advantage of me so I will always stand
我的优势所以我会永远站立
my ground and no man will ever push me
我的理由， 没有人会永远推我
around guess what happened in their
周围猜猜他们身上发生了什么
marriage
婚姻
yeah it just turned into escalating any
是的它只是变成了升级
time he would express his opinion she
他会表达自己的意见
came right back with a very strong
很快就回来了
opinion and it was like who could out
意见，这就像是谁可以出去
curse the other the fastest as possible
尽可能快地诅咒对方
telling someone off attacking verbally
告诉别人口头攻击
name-calling versus the slow burn maybe
打电话给慢速烧伤可能
all of that stuff going on on the inside
所有这些都在内部发生
it's like clamming up when we do
这就像我们这样做时的吵架
conflict resolution we talk about people
冲突解决我们 谈论的人
10 toward to two extremes you either go
你要么 走向两个极端
in attack mode or you go into withdrawal
在攻击模式下或你进入撤退
mode well maybe you're more the
模式很好也许你是更多的
withdrawal person or your council Lee is
撤回人或你的理事会李是
more the withdrawal person and you're
更多的退出人员和你
frustrated irritated disgusted glaring
沮丧烦躁厌恶的怒视
huffing snorting that's an interesting
喘着粗气这是一个有趣的
one
一
the huffing snorting Scripture even uses
愤怒的吸食圣经甚至使用
that one of the Hebrew words is quite
那个希伯来语中的一个词是相当的
picturesque for for snorting and another
风景如画，另一个
word I'd add here is seething
我在这里添加的词是沸腾的
maybe you just feel like the slow burn
也许你只是觉得慢慢燃烧
is really going on on the inside you
真的是在你的内心
feel like you're just seething on the
感觉你只是在沸腾
inside so here's what we want to do we
在里面所以这就是我们想做的事情
want to pull back the cover let's let's
我想拉回封面让我们来吧
just look at this and say okay Lord
看看这个，说好吧，主啊
expose this what is this stuff that's
揭露这是什么东西
going on so here's some biblical
继续下去，这里有一些圣经
principles and there's all just a wide
原则而且这一切都很广泛
variety of biblical principles that
各种圣经原则
Scripture speaks to related to anger one
圣经说相关激怒一个
of my favorite counseling verses when
我最喜欢的辅导经文
I'm trying to urge people to deal with
我试图促使人们应对
issues is that one that's in bold print
问题是粗体印刷的问题
they're in your notes and it says dude
他们在你的笔记中，它说伙计
and do not participate in the unfruitful
不参加徒劳
deeds of darkness but instead even
黑暗的行为，但相反甚至
expose them sin in our lives is like the
在我们的生活中暴露他们的罪就像是
creepy crawlies right it's like the
令人毛骨悚然的爬行就像是
roaches it's like the rats it likes to
蟑螂就像它喜欢的老鼠
stay in dark damp places scripture says
圣经说，留在黑暗潮湿的地方
shine the light of God's Word on the
照亮神的话语
dark areas of life come out into the
黑暗的生活领域进入了
open expose them expose the unfruitful
公开暴露他们暴露无益
works of darkness so I'm going to go
黑暗的作品所以我要走了
through some of these rather quickly
通过其中一些相当快
just because there's some that I really
只是因为有一些我真的
need to focus on in particular so I'm
需要特别 关注，所以我
gonna read some pretty quickly and then
然后快速读一些
we're gonna slow down on D and E in this
我们将 在这里 放慢D和E的 速度
first list so it's a deed of the flesh
第一个清单， 所以它是肉体的契约
Galatians chapter 5 19 to 20 if you've
加拉太书第5章19至20，如果你的话
never realized it before that's the
在那之前从未意识到这一点
fruit of the Spirit list and realize
精神的果实 清单并实现
that right before the fruit of the
就在那之前的果实
spirit list is the fruit of the flesh
灵魂清单是肉体的果实
list and just to get myself ready for
列出，只是让自己准备好
this presentation I went back to refresh
这个演讲我回去刷新了
my memory on the fruit of the flesh list
我记忆中的肉体清单
and about half the list is you could say
你可以说，大约一半的名单
is related to anger there's all kinds of
与愤怒有关， 各种各样
words that are used related to anger and
与愤怒有关的词语
the fruit of the flesh list and anger is
肉列表和愤怒 的 水果
natural to the human heart
对人类心脏是自然的
anger involves thoughts and intentions
愤怒涉及思想和意图
and then let's slow down and think about
然后让我们慢下来思考一下
this one term with me to James chapter 4
这一个词与我同詹姆斯第4章
I want to start proposing some questions
我想开始提出一些问题
and it'll be a whole lot of questions
这将是一个很多问题
later on in the presentation to help us
稍后在演讲中帮助我们
deal with anger but James for a lot of
处理愤怒，但詹姆斯很多
churches need to read these verses to
教会需要阅读这些经文
understand what's going on with the
明白是怎么回事了
conflict that's going on in our church
我们教会正在发生的冲突
James chapter 4 says this verse 1 what
詹姆斯第4章说这第1节是什么
is the source of quarrels and conflicts
是争吵和冲突的根源
among you when you like to know the
当你想知道的时候
answer to that hey-ya what is the source
回答那个嘿呀是什么来源
of the quarrels and conflicts among you
你们之间的争吵和冲突
here's what James writes is not the
这是詹姆斯写的不是
source your and here's the word Hayden a
来源你和这里是海登一词
what where do we get from that hedonism
我们从那个享乐主义中得到了什么？
is not the source your pleasures that
不是源的乐趣是
wage here's the word and when I read
这里是工资，当我读到的时候
this I say wow the Bible's got me
我说哇圣经让我感到惊讶
figured out the Lord has me figured out
想通了主让我想通了
here's the word wage Stratego what word
这里是工资Stratego这个词用什么词
do we get from that strategy so what's
我们从那个策略中得到了什么呢？
the source of quarrels and conflicts is
争吵和冲突的根源是
not the source your pleasures that are
不是你的快乐的来源
strategizing war and your members so
运筹帷幄战争和你的成员等等
I've got this thing going on inside of
我已经把这件事发生了
me of how do I get what I want and
我的我怎么得到我想要的东西，
thinking through your inner person is
通过你的内心思考是
active according to Hebrews chapter 4 it
根据希伯来书第4章的说法活跃起来
has thoughts and intentions and we
有想法和意图，我们
strategize how do I get the things I
策略化我如何得到我的东西
want or how do I avoid the things I
想要或如何避免我的事情
don't want and then he says you lust and
不要，然后他说你欲望和
do not have and that's the word
没有，就是这个词
epithelia it's strong desire you have
上皮， 你有强烈的愿望
strong desire and do not have next time
强烈的欲望，没有下一次
you're angry whether it's external or
无论是外在的还是外在的，你都生气了
internal two simple questions to ask
内部两个简单的问题要问
your self it's really the same question
你的自我真的是同一个问题
but I'm just inversing it what am i
但我只是反正它是什么我
wanting that I'm not getting what am I
我想要的不是我
getting that I'm not wanting what am i
得到那个我不想要的是我
wanting that I'm not getting if it has
想要我没有得到它
to do with my pleasures that are
与我的快乐有关
strategizing in my inner person because
因为，在我内心的人制定战略
of my desires my strong desires what am
我渴望的是我强烈的欲望
i wanting that I'm not getting what am I
我想我不会得到我
getting that I'm not wanting and then
得到那个我不想要的话
scripture says and I'm going to show you
经文说，我要告诉你
a
一个
very helpful diagram to think about this
想一想非常有用的图表
that anger is caused by not being able
愤怒是不能够引起
to attain our pride for selfish goals
为了自私的目标而获得自豪感
and then anger never accomplishes God's
然后愤怒永远不会完成上帝的
righteous ends very clear in Scripture
在圣经中，义人的结局非常清楚
now let's go to a diagram let's think
现在让我们来看一个让我们思考的图表
about this as a way to think about
关于这样的一种方式来思考
what's going on and I'm gonna give you
这是怎么回事，我要去给你
some I'm just gonna walk you through it
有些我会带你走过去
and then I'll give you some practical
然后我会给你一些实用的
applications of how to use this diagram
应用程序如何使用此图表
also but then I want to give you a
也是后来我想给你一个
scenario we're gonna go back to traffic
我们要回到交通状况
again since that's something we all have
因为那是我们所拥有 的东西
to deal with here in the LA area and
在洛杉矶地区和 这里处理
then maybe if I have time we'll deal
那么也许如果我有时间我们会处理
with I'll give you an illustration with
我会给你一个插图
child rearing also so we're trying to
育儿也是如此，所以我们正努力
picture we're trying to take seriously
图片我们正在努力认真对待
Hebrews 4:12 that says my heart has
希伯来书4:12说我心里有
thoughts and intentions so this is
想法和意图所以这是
picturing what's causing pressure in my
想象一下我的压力是什么造成的
life what's the situation in my life
生活是我生活中的情况
that's causing pressure think of some
这会引起一些人的压力
other biblical words for a moment for
其他一些圣经的话语
the situation's of life that caused
引起的生活状况
pressure we might use word like words
压力我们可能会像文字一样用词
like trials and I would urge you for the
类似的试验，我会劝你了
the the for the purposes of biblical
出于圣经的目的
counseling to stop thinking of trials as
辅导停止试验的思想为
just the big things that happen in your
只是你身上发生的重大事情
life and think of trials as how are you
生活和思考试验你是怎样的
responding to the pressures of life if
如果，应对生活的压力
you start thinking of trials that way
你开始以这种方式思考试验
the Sirk normal circumstances of life
Sirk正常的生活环境
that are causing pressures it'll change
这会带来压力，它会改变
the way you read your Bible because then
那时你读圣经的方式
you start reading okay how did David
你开始阅读好吧大卫怎么样？
respond to the pressures of his life how
应对他生活中的压力如何
did Paul respond to the normal pressures
保罗是否回应了正常的压力
of his life so in our pressure box up
他的生活如此在我们的压力盒中
there at the top of the diagram you
在图的顶部你
could say for the sake of our discussion
可以说是为了我们的讨论
traffic traffic that's causing pressure
造成压力的 交通堵塞
in my life now notice the right-hand
在我的生活中现在注意到右手
side of the diagram and there's a line
图的侧，并有一个线
right down through the middle what
右向下穿过中间什么
that's picturing those two sides the
那是在描绘那两个方面
right-hand side and the bottom are
右手边和底边都是
picturing your inner person
想象你的内心
so that's hebrews 4:12 the thoughts and
这是希伯来书4:12的想法和
intentions of your heart right hand side
你心中的意图右手边
is your inner person what's going on in
是你内在的人正在发生什么
the inner person as I am under this
内部的人，因为我这下
pressure in my life and then what comes
生活中的压力，然后是什么
out in my outer person now I'm back
现在我回来了
around on the left-hand side of what how
周围的左侧怎么什么
do I respond how do I react to the
我怎么回应我的反应
pressures of life and then notice the
生活的压力，然后注意到
arrows if I respond in a godly way it
箭如果我以敬虔的方式回应 它
helps me deal with the pressure of life
帮助我应对生活压力
but if I do not respond in a godly way
但如果我没有以敬虔的方式回应
it can further exasperate the problem
它可以进一步加剧这个问题
especially if you're someone that
特别是如果你是那样的人
struggles with road rage out on the 405
在405上挣扎着狂暴的道路
that can really exasperate the problem
这真的可以激怒这个问题
if you don't respond right to the
如果你没有回应权利
pressures of life notice also the tree
生命的压力也注意到树
and let's go to Matthew 12 just to kind
让我们去马修12只是为了善良
of capture this a little bit scripture
抓住这一点经文
thinks of us as inner person and outer
认为我们是内在的人和外在的人
person root and fruit body and soul now
人的根和果实的身体和灵魂现在
the reason why in dr. Khoo Kouros
之所以在博士。 Khoo Kouros
statements I said it was a worldview
陈述我说这是世界观
statement he said it has to do with the
声明说它与做
chemicals in your brain well he's coming
他脑子里的化学物质很好，他来了
at this probably I don't know this
在这可能我不知道这一点
physician or this researcher but he's
医生或这位研究员，但他是
probably coming at this and question of
可能会出现这个问题
anger or road rage or intermittent
愤怒或道路愤怒或间歇性
explosive disorder from a worldview that
从世界观爆炸性的疾病，
we would call a monastic worldview that
我们称之为修道院的世界观
you're just a single part being there is
你只是一个单独的部分
no such thing as an immaterial part of
没有非物质的一部分
you called the soul but according to
你打电话给灵魂，但根据
scripture we are bipartite we are two
经文我们是二分的我们是两个
parts
部分
you're not just the brain with chemicals
你不只是化学物质的大脑
you have an immaterial part of you that
你有一个无关紧要的部分
scripture calls the soul or calls the
经文呼唤灵魂或召唤灵魂
heart or sometimes it uses the word mind
心脏或有时它使用心灵这个词
you have an inner person and you have an
你有一个内在的人，你有一个
outer person Matthew chapter 12 says
外面的人马太福音12章说
this using the idea of the tree with the
这种使用与树的想法
root system Matthew 12:33 either make
根系马太福音12:33 或者说
the tree good and it's fruit good or
树好，它的果实好或
make the tree rotten in its
使树烂了
rootin for the tree is known by its
rootin的树被 称为其
fruit and the Lord's going right after
水果和主正在追求
the Pharisees here so he says you brood
法利赛人在这里，所以他说你们
of vipers how can you being evil speak
你怎么能成为邪恶的说话
what is good for the mouth speaks out of
什么对嘴有益说出来
that which fills the heart the good man
那能使善人满心的东西
out of his good treasure brings forth
出他的好宝带来了
what is good the evil man out of his
这个邪恶的人有多好
evil treasure brings forth what is evil
邪恶的宝藏带来了什么是邪恶的
inner person outer person root and fruit
内心人外根和果实
the way I speak reveals something that
我说话的方式揭示了一些东西
is going on in the heart and I would
心里正在发生，我愿意
also add to that statements so it's not
也添加到那些语句，所以它不是
only out of the abundance of the heart
只是出于内心的丰富
the mouth speaks out of the abundance of
嘴里说出丰富的
the heart the mouth doesn't speak out of
嘴里没有说出来的心
the abundance of the heart you clam up
你吵起来 的心脏丰富
there's something going on in the inner
内心正在发生一些事情
person as to why you respond to the
人为什么你回应
pressures of life by clamming up by
由 clamming了生活的压力
seething on the inside and I'll make
在里面沸腾，我会做
some suggestions in a little bit as to
在一点点来 的一些建议
why that might be but it has to do with
为什么会这样，但它与此有关
the very bottom thoughts and intentions
最底层的想法和意图
the motives desires and once of the
动机的欲望和曾经的
heart now let's just walk through this
心脏现在让我们步行穿过这个
and think about traffic for a moment
并考虑一下交通
then I have another illustration to give
然后我有另一个例子给予
you so bad traffic on the 405 somebody
你这么糟糕的交通405在某人身上
cuts you off what's going on in your
切断你身上发生的事情
thought life or I could also add in that
想到生活， 或者我也可以加入其中
section their thoughts what's going on
他们的想法是什么
and this would kind of be the overlap
这有点重叠
between the right side and the bottom
在右侧和底部之间
attitudes what's your attitude about
态度你怎么看态度
that
那
so someone cuts you off and the type of
所以有人会切断你的类型
stuff that goes through your mind may be
经历过你脑海中的东西可能是
something like this hey buddy I'm in
像这样的东西嘿伙计我在
just as much of a hurry as you nobody's
一样多着急的，你没有人在
gonna push me around and what could be
要推我到底是什么
going on down at the bottom of the
怎么回事下来的底部
diagram I deserve respect nobody is
图我值得尊重没有人
gonna push me around I'm not gonna let
要推开我，我不会放过
anybody control me like that
任何人都这样控制我
so what do you do maybe maybe the
所以你也许做什么呢？
person's tailgating you and so they're
这个人跟你有关，所以他们就是这样
coming up right behind you and they're
在你身后出现，他们是
tailgating you and you're not going to
尾随你，你不会
be pushed around that's the attitude or
围绕推动的态度或
the
该
want or the desire that's going on in
想要或这回事的愿望
your heart so what do you do you bump
你的心脏，所以你做什么撞击
your brakes because you're gonna send
你的刹车，因为你要发送
this guy a message get off my tail now
这家伙现在有消息从我的尾巴上下来
that can be really dangerous going at 70
在70岁时可能真的很危险
or 80 miles an hour out on the 405 not
或者在405不是每小时80英里
here not that anybody here goes 80 miles
这里并没有任何人走80英里
an hour out on the 405 I'm sure that
一个小时出来就405我敢肯定，
that is not the case because we're all
事实并非如此，因为我们都是
followers of Christ we don't go 80 miles
基督的追随者我们不走80英里
an hour out on the 405 but just kind of
在405上一个小时，但只是一点点
you know maybe that this might happen
你知道也许会发生这种情况
and you bump your brakes and you know
和你碰到你的刹车，你知道
what could happen the arrow further
什么可能进一步发生箭头
exasperates the problem let's what
激怒问题让我们做什么
switch to a parenting illustration what
切换到育儿插图是什么
could be going on in the heart of the
可能会继续在...的核心
angry person I would say the theme in
愤怒的人我会说主题
the heart there might be things like I
心里可能有像我这样的东西
live for respect
为尊重而生
I desire respect I demand respect or I
我希望尊重我要求尊重或我
am in control nobody else is in control
在控制中， 没有其他人可以控制
of my life I am in control of my life
我的生活中，我掌控着自己的生活
and that might have to that might reveal
而这可能需要揭示
what are the thoughts and intentions
什么是想法和意图
that are going on in the mind or in the
这是在脑海里或在脑海中发生的
soul of the angry person let me give you
愤怒的人的灵魂让我给你
one other illustration you come here's
你来这里的另一个例子
the situation you come home from work
你下班回家的情况
let's say you're the parents of young
让我们说你是年轻人的父母
children mom has been with the children
孩子妈妈一直和孩子们在一起
all day long you come in let's say it's
你进来的整天让我们说是的
the husband comes in he's been with
丈夫进来他一直在
people all day long and he doesn't want
人们整天和他不希望
to talk because he's been dealing with
说话， 因为他一直在处理
people all day long
人们整天
she's looking forward to talking she's
她很期待和她说话
looking forward to daddy taking over
期待爸爸接管
with the children now so he walks in and
现在跟孩子们一起走进去
he wants to go sit in the chair and
他想坐在椅子上
breed or whatever it is that he does to
品种或不管它是什么 ，他不来
unwind but in between daddy and mommy
放松，但在爸爸和妈妈之间
we've got a child misbehaving mom is
我们有一个孩子行为不端的妈妈
doing her best to ignore the child's
做她最好忽略 了孩子的
misbehavior because she's been dealing
不正当，因为她一直在交易
with the child all day long dad isn't
和孩子一整天都没有爸爸
doing his best to ignore the child's
尽力忽略孩子的
misbehavior because I've been dealing
不端行为，因为我一直在交易
with people all day long
与人们整天
I need to relax right now what's going
我现在需要放松一下
on in the thoughts and intentions of the
在 的 思想和意图
heart and Europe we're already getting
心和欧洲我们已经得到了
the response over their thought life
他们思想生活的反应
things like I need to relax this is my
像我需要放松的事情就是我的
time to chill out I didn't come home to
时间放松我没有回家
have to discipline children what might
必须训练孩子可能的
be going on in the wants and desires of
继续前进的愿望和欲望
the heart at the bottom it's time to
在底部的心脏是时候了
relax I just want some relaxation I
放松我只想放松一下
would call that a comfort loving theme
会称之为舒适的主题
that there may be as a comfort loving
这可能是一种舒适的爱
theme going on in the person's heart I
主题继续在人的心中我
live I desire I want comfort what am i
我渴望我想要安慰我是什么
wanting that I'm not getting what am I
我想要的不是我
getting that I'm not wanting and you
得到我不想和你
know how wrong responses kyndley further
知道kyndley的反应有多么错误
exasperate the problem as mom and dad
像妈妈和爸爸一样激怒了这个问题
start to confront each other as to why
开始彼此面对，为什么
one of them is not dealing with the
其中一人是不是对付
child
儿童
this diagram let me give you a practical
这个图让我给你一个实用的
use of this diagram it's based on
使用此图表是基于
Hebrews 4:12 you can actually use this
希伯来书4:12你实际上可以用这个
diagram to take notes in counseling I've
我在咨询中做笔记的图表
used this this has been drawn on many
使用过这个已经吸引了很多人
Starbucks napkins this has been drawn on
星巴克餐巾纸已被吸引
many McDonald's napkins as I'm sitting
我正坐着的很多麦当劳餐巾纸
there working with people and I'm just
与人合作，我只是
trying to figure out okay what is going
试图弄清楚会发生什么
on in this person's life and then the
在这个人的生活然后
way that I typically use it is I fill in
我通常使用它的方式是我填写
what's causing the pressure what is this
是什么造成的压力， 这是什么
person's typical thought life how are
人的典型思想生活是怎样的
they responding left hand side and then
他们回应左手边然后
what are both the thoughts and their
什么是思想和他们的
responses telling me about the motives
回复告诉我动机
of the heart what is this person living
心脏的这是什么人的生活
for drawing this diagram could also be
绘制此图也可以
helpful then for coming up with your
有帮助然后提出你的
next agenda for dealing with the person
处理这个人的下一个议程
same situation may God doesn't promise
同样的情况可以神不答应
that the situation is going to change
情况会发生变化
same situation but what would godly
同样的情况，但什么会敬虔
thoughts look like what would godly
想法看起来像是敬虔的
attitudes be what would godly intentions
态度是敬虔的意图
be and desires
是和欲望
what would godly responses be and you
什么是敬虔的回应和你
can use this to actually make up an
可以用它来实际组成一个
agenda for dealing with the person that
议程打交道的这个人是
you're counseling and disciple encoder
你是辅导和门徒编码器
back from identifying sinful anger
从识别罪恶的愤怒回来
here's some other things that scripture
这里有其他一些经文
says it's expressed in our thoughts body
说它在我们的思想体中表达出来
language speech and actions remember dr.
语言和行动记得博士。
Jones's Robert Jones's definition it's a
琼斯的罗伯特琼斯的定义是一个
whole person response it involves a lack
整个人的反应都涉及到缺乏
of self-control let me make a real quick
自我控制让我快速实现
comment about that when we think about
当我们考虑时，对此进行评论
self-control we think of self-control as
我们把自我控制视为自我控制
an outward body thing that we have to
我们必须要做的外在的身体
learn let me just inject into your
学会让我注入你的
thinking the idea that there is a thing
想到有一件事 的想法
called emotional self-control not only
所谓的自我情绪控制，不仅
learning physical self-control but being
学习身体自我控制， 但存在
a person that learns emotional
一个学习情感的人
self-control anger is always accompanied
总是伴随着自我控制的愤怒
by other sins when it's tolerated it
当它容忍它时，由其他罪恶
just compounds things if not dealt with
如果没有处理，只会复合事物
anger will turn into something worse now
愤怒现在会变得更糟
here's some examine examination
这里有一些考试
questions for you these would be things
问题对你来说这些都是事情
for yourself or for your counsel II just
为了你自己或你的忠告我只是
thinking through this for yourself
为自己思考这个
notice the wording it's not just I'm
注意这个措辞不仅仅是我
presently angry with the souls really
现在真的对灵魂生气了
tricky and if I just worded it that way
如果我只是这样措辞，那就太棘手了
is there anyone I'm presently angry with
有没有人，我现在生气
some of you go I'm not an angry person
你们当中有些人我不是一个愤怒的人
but it's it's what's going on on the
但这就是它正在发生的事情
inside so we add the word frustrated
在里面所以我们添加沮丧的词
there what am i angry with them about
我对他们有什么生气的感觉
how have I dealt with and responded to
我是如何处理和回应的
that person just trying to start to
那个人只是想开始
think practically to uncover what's
实际上想要发现什么是
going on what do I typically do when I'm
我正在做什么我通常做什么
angry and what have been some of the
生气了，有些什么了
results of my anger I would urge you
我的愤怒的结果我会敦促你
again to not let your soul off the hook
再次不要让你的灵魂脱离困境
and say well I'm not angry so that's
并且说得好，我不生气，所以那是
getting at you no I I don't hit people
getting你没有II不打人
etc well what does your seething do what
等等你的沸腾做了什么
does the frustration that's built up do
这是否是内置了无奈做
on the inside and we know the answer to
在里面，我们知道答案
those kind of questions right it builds
它构建的那些问题
up barriers with other people if you
如果你，与其他人的障碍
just keep that frustration that's
只要保持那种挫败感
seething on the inside the barriers go
在障碍物里面沸腾了
up between you and other people do
在你和其他人 之间 做
others see me as a critical or impatient
其他人认为我是批评者或不耐烦者
person and I have in your notes be brave
我和你在笔记中的人是勇敢的
ask them ask your spouse and then tell
请他们问你的配偶，然后告诉他们
them it's alright to be truthful and
他们这是正常的真实 ，
really mean it
真的是这个意思
more questions here's a here's one I
这里有更多问题，这是我的一个
don't have in the notes that I was
没有在我的笔记
thinking about as I was going through it
想着我正在经历它
are you an easy person to live with are
你是一个容易接受的人吗？
you a difficult person to live with you
你是一个和你一起生活的难民
a high-maintenance person are you a
你是一个高维护的人
low-maintenance person I'm afraid a lot
低维护的人我很害怕
of times for my wife I'm a
对我妻子来说，我是一个时代
high-maintenance person pray for my wife
高维护的人为 我的妻子祈祷
rose more questions and then we're gonna
提出更多问题然后我们会
get to some more solutions think about
得到一些更多的解决方案考虑一下
the last five times you were angry and
你生气了过去五年时间，
these type of questions are getting at
这些类型的问题正在进行中
patterns what were you thinking so
模式你在想什么？
there's we're getting at thoughts and
我们正在思考和思考
intentions again what are the types of
意图再次是什么类型
things that that seem to provoke you to
那些似乎引起你注意的事情
anger let me stop and show you a
愤怒让我停下来告诉你一个
homework assignment the last session I
作业分配上一节我
showed you this homework assignment so
向您展示了这个家庭作业等等
this was back in the extra handouts at
这回到了额外的讲义中
the end of the last outline and I didn't
最后一个大纲的结尾，我没有
take the time to explain how to use it
花点时间解释如何使用它
then but I can go through it right now
那么我现在可以通过它
pretty quickly so I've used this very
非常快，所以我非常喜欢这个
often with people struggling with anger
经常与人们在愤怒中挣扎
and it's trying to get them to see okay
而且它试图让他们看到没问题
what was the situation what was going on
发生了什么事情
and I'm I'm using this homework
而我正在使用这个功课
assignment as a journaling homework
作为日记作业的作业
assignment so that they start to pick up
任务， 以便他们开始接受
the patterns in their life and part of
在他们的生活和一部分的模式
defeating anger part of growing in grace
击败愤怒的一部分， 在恩典中成长
as you fight against anger is learning
当你与愤怒作斗争正在学习
to become a more self-aware person so
成为一个更自我意识的人如此
that you start heading it off earlier
你开始早些开始
and start responding in a biblical way
并以圣经的方式开始回应
earlier so what's going on how are you
早些时候你怎么样？
responding to what's going on in your
回应中发生了什么事情 你
emotions actions and reactions what do
情绪的行动和反应是做什么的
you think about what's going on what do
你想想发生了什么事情
you think about God what are you
你想到上帝你是什​​么人
thinking about others what are you
想着别人你是什么人
thinking about yourself what are you
想着你自己是什么
thinking about life and what are you
思考生活，你是什么
wanting goals desires wants demands
想要目标欲望需要
you have a person who's angry and when
你有一个生气的人，什么时候生气
they respond was sinful anger they start
他们回应是他们开始的罪恶愤怒
filling this out and you as the
填写这个和你一样
counselor look at these and you're
顾问看看这些，你就是
starting to look for patterns you can
开始寻找你可以的模式
help your counsel II become more self
帮助你的律师II变得更加自我
aware and they start seeing wow they're
意识到并且他们开始看到他们的哇
really are once and desires going on in
真的是一次，欲望继续下去
my heart that I wasn't aware of it's not
我的心，我不知道它不是
just about chemicals in my brain and I
关于我脑中的化学物质和我
can't help myself because I have some
我不能帮助自己，因为我有一些
kind of a disease called anger no there
一种疾病叫做愤怒的不存在
really is once thoughts and intentions
真的是曾经的想法和意图
going on in my heart so one more the
在我的心里继续这么一次
last five times what kinds of things
什么样的东西最后五次
provoke you to anger do I need to keep
引起你的愤怒我需要保持
track in the next few weeks just gave
跟踪在接下来的几个星期刚刚给出
you a practical idea of how to do that
你是如何做到这一点的实际想法
write down what you're thinking just
写下你在想什么
gave you a practical homework assignment
给了你一份实用的家庭作业
on that one and then how many of these
在那一个，然后有多少这些
situations are precipitated by something
情况是由某种东西引发的
else I'm doing wrong
否则我做错了
there's laziness in my life leading to
我生命中的懒惰导致了
this poor time management etc and then
这个可怜的时间管理等，然后
I've been wanting to build up to this
我一直想要建立起来
and to think about how do we think about
并思考我们如何思考
rights whether it is external anger or
权利无论是外部愤怒还是外部愤怒
its internal seething and frustration I
它的内心沸腾和沮丧我
can guarantee to you there are things
可以向你保证有东西
going on on the inside that you think
继续你认为的内部
you deserve that are your rights let me
你应得的是你的权利让我
give you some ideas what are things that
给你一些想法是什么
you believe you deserve and then let's
你相信你应该得到，然后让我们
think about what do we do with these
想想我们 这些做
rights that we have on the inside how do
我们内部的权利如何做
we think about rights I'll just put a
我们考虑的权利我只会提出一个
whole bunch up so I have the right I
整个团队，所以我有正确的我
have the need to be free of intense
有必要摆脱激烈
problems and pressures and with all of
问题和压力以及所有问题
these you could add it would be wise to
这些你可以添加它是明智的
ask yourself what does this really
问问自己这是真的
represent in my life what am i wanting I
在我的生活中代表我想要的是什么
have a right to privacy I have a right
我有权利享有隐私权
to hold and express my opinion that
持有并表达我的意见
sounds like the woman that I told you
听起来像我告诉你的女人
about earlier boy did she believe that I
关于早先的男孩，她相信我
have a right to money in possessions and
在财产和财产上有钱
to use them any way I want
以任何我想要的方式使用它们
I have a right to plan my schedule no
我有权计划我的日程安排
one else planned my schedule I have a
其他人计划我的日程表我有一个
right to be respected I need I have a
得到尊重的权利我需要我有一个
right to friends to be loved and
对朋友的爱和权利
accepted to be understood and listened
接受理解和倾听
to to be supported for supported and
支持和支持
cared for I do quite a bit with conflict
我非常关心冲突
resolution and in peacemaker ministries
决议和和平缔造者部
we try to teach people that in every
我们试图教导每个人
conflict and we're obviously talking
冲突，我们显然在说话
about conflict here because anger has to
关于这里的冲突，因为愤怒必须
do with tensions and relationships
处理紧张和关系
whether it is internal and the person
无论是内部还是人
may not even know you're angry because
甚至可能都不知道你生气，因为
you're just it's all kept on the inside
你只是把它放在里面
and you're so frustrated with the person
和你在一起的人很沮丧
and you haven't even expressed it or
而你甚至没有表达过它
whether it's external anger it has to do
无论是外部的愤怒它做
with tension in relationships so we
关系紧张所以我们
teach people when there's tensions and
当紧张局势和时候教人
relationships that you have
你有的关系
opportunities here like you wouldn't
这里的机会就像你不会
have at other times here's the three
在其他时间这里是三个
opportunities that are built into every
每个人都有机会
conflict situation
冲突局势
1st Corinthians 10:31 says whether you
哥林多前书10:31说你是否
eat or drink or whatever you do do all
吃或喝或做你所做的一切
of the glory of God do all of the glory
上帝的荣耀 ，做所有的荣耀
of God
上帝
well if Paul really meant what he wrote
好吧，如果保罗真的意味着他写的东西
whether you eat or drink or whatever you
不管你吃或喝，或任何你
do
做
that would include conflict wouldn't it
这将包括冲突不会
do it for the glory of God so how do I
为了荣耀上帝而这样做，我该怎么做
approach this conflict so that God gets
接近这场冲突，以便上帝得到
glory now wouldn't that change your
荣耀现在不会改变你的
perspective on tensions and
对紧张局势的看法
relationships right from the beginning
从一开始就是关系
second opportunity built into every
每个人都有第二次机会
conflict how can I serve others
冲突我怎样才能为他人服务
Philippians chapter 2 says look not out
腓立比书第2章说看不出来
for the meat your own need to enter your
为了你自己需要进入你的肉
own interest but also the interests of
自己的兴趣，但也有利益
others Philippians chapter 2 verses 3 &
其他腓立比书第2章3节＆
4 how can I serve others in this
4我怎样才能在此服务他人
conflict amazing story in John 13 of our
在约翰福音13章中我们的冲突令人惊叹
Lord being a servant the night before he
在他之前的一个晚上，主是一个仆人
was going to be crucified third
将被钉在十字架上
opportunity so glorify God serve others
机会如此荣耀上帝为他人服务
third opportunity built into every
每个人都有第三次机会
conflict how do I grow in Christ
冲突如何在基督里成长？
likeness built into every conflict our
我们每次冲突都融入了相似之处
opportunities to grow in your
你的成长机会
relationship with the Lord now let let's
现在让我们与主的关系
think about rights if I have those three
如果我有这三个，请考虑权利
opportunities in view I'm gonna glorify
我认为的机会我要荣耀
God I'm gonna serve other people and I'm
上帝我会为其他人服务而我
gonna grow in Christ's likeness what
要像基督的样式一样成长
does that do to our rights don't our
这样做对我们的权利不是我们的
rights die
权利死亡
and I think that's the answer to how do
我认为这就是答案，怎么办
we think about rights biblically is the
我们以 圣经的方式思考权利
Lord's calling me to be a servant to
主叫我做个仆人
glorify Him etc and I realized that
荣耀他等我意识到了这一点
that's pretty radical thinking and
这是非常激进的思考和
you're gonna have to wrestle through
你会不得不通过搏斗
that on your own let's talk about
你可以自己谈谈
transformation how do you change and
转型如何改变和改变
we're gonna finish by talking about
我们来谈谈要去完成
before during and after before let me
之前和之后让我
just put a whole bunch of things up here
只是把一大堆东西在这里
and we'll work our way through it
我们将我们的工作方式，通过它
one too many clicks there so I have to
那里有太多的点击，所以我必须这样做
go back again confess past sins of anger
再回去交代过去的愤怒罪
to God and others don't just call it a
对上帝和其他人不只是称之为
physical issue any longer I've sinned
身体问题不再是我犯了罪
against God in others pray for God's
别人反对上帝为上帝祈祷
help right out biblical thoughts to
帮助正确的圣经思想
replace wrong thoughts let me stop and
更换错误的想法让我停下来，
talk about that one for a moment let's
让我们谈谈那个
say there's a husband who's just really
说有一个真正的丈夫
struggling with ceasing seething and
努力停止沸腾和
frustration about his wife often what
关于他妻子的挫折经常是什么
I'll do is you have them go to
我会做的就是你让他们去
Philippians 4:8 in Philippians 4:8 says
腓立比书4：8中腓立比书4：8说
think of things that are good and pure
想想那些美好而纯洁的事物
and honest and good repute and I'll have
诚实和良好的声誉，我会
that husband make a list of the positive
那个丈夫列出了积极的一面
things that he can think about about his
他能想到的关于他的事情
wife and carry that list around with him
妻子和他一起带着那份名单
and of course the motive has to be right
当然，动机必须是正确的
that I want to do this because I know
因为我知道 ，我想这样做
this is what the Lord wants me to do so
这是主希望我这样做的
coming from the motive of I want to do
来自我想做的动机
this this is not just behaviorism I'm
这不仅仅是我的行为主义
gonna somehow cognitive-behavioral II
以某种方式认知行为II
change my thinking no from the motive of
从动机的角度 改变我的思想
the inner person I want to do what the
内心的人我想做什么的
Lord wants me to do I'm gonna work on my
上帝要我做什么我要上我的工作
thinking about my wife and you may have
考虑我的妻子，你可能有
to wrestle with him to even come up with
与他搏斗甚至想出来
some things for that list
该列表的一些东西
you can like does she do your laundry
你可以喜欢她洗衣服吗？
etc whatever it takes to get on that
等等，无论如何都需要
list things for him to be working on his
列出让他为他工作的事情
thinking related to his wife Philippians
思考与他的妻子腓立比人有关
chapter 4 verse 8 memorize appropriate
第4 章第8节 记忆合适
verses let the Word of God do its
经文让上帝的话语做到了
transformation power in your soul seek
你灵魂中的转化力量寻求
to put on a loving and humble thoughts
提出一个充满爱心和谦卑的想法
and actions toward others next list of
和下一个列表的行动
things to do ahead of time back one more
提前做的事情还有一件事要做
determined godly desires and goals study
确定敬虔的欲望和目标研究
God's patience and long-suffering be
上帝的耐心和长期的痛苦是
alert ready to exercise self-control and
警惕准备好自我控制和
change your thinking and then the last
改变你的想法，然后是最后一点
thing have accountability remember the
事情有责任记得
Ephesians 5 principle expose the
以弗所书5原则揭露了
unfruitful works of darkness so get some
无益的黑暗作品所以得到一些
accountability for this and then
对此负责
proverbs 22 warns us about associating
谚语22警告我们关于联想
with other angry individuals that just
和其他愤怒的人一样
kind of spur you on and and and egg you
有点刺激你，和你一起吃蛋
on and then number 11 learn to handle
，然后 11号学会处理
relationship issues biblically over on
圣经关系问题
the tables they're these wonderful
桌子他们是这些美妙的
little brochures that look like this
看起来像这样的 小册子
peacemaking principles and they have in
他们所拥有的和平原则
these brochures a way to work through
这些小册子是一种可行的方法
issues with people rather than just
人们的问题而不仅仅是问题
reacting to individuals and one of the
对个人和其中一个人 做出反应
principles I love to teach is called the
我喜欢教的原则叫做
pause principle the pause principle
暂停原则暂停原则
instead of reacting or internalizing
而不是反应或内化
when I have a person that internalizes I
当我有一个内化我的人
know I need to teach them good conflict
知道我需要教他们好冲突
resolution principles rather than
决议原则而不是
internalizing or rather than reacting
内化或反应
how do you sit down and have a sane
你怎么坐下来保持理智
conversation with people the pause
与人交谈暂停
principle Philippians chapter 2 look not
原则菲律宾第2章看起来不是
out for your own interest but also the
为了你自己的利益而且还有
interests of others that's the key verse
他人的利益是关键的经文
for the pause principle so prepare how
暂停原则所以准备如何
do you prepare praying for the person
你准备为这个人祈祷吗？
praying for the Lord to work in their
祈求主在他们的工作中工作
heart praying for the right timing kind
心为正确的时间祈祷
of anticipate what the other person is
期待对方是什么
going to say
要说
and then start off positive by affirming
然后通过肯定开始积极
the relationship if this is with your
如果这与你的关系
spouse and you have some tense things to
配偶， 你有一些紧张的事情
talk about start off with honey this is
谈谈从蜂蜜开始这是
not about the longevity of our marriage
不是关于我们婚姻的长寿
I love you and I'm committed to our
我爱你，我致力于我们
marriage but we have some things we need
婚姻， 但我们有一些我们需要的东西
to talk about start off positive and
谈开始积极
affirm the relationship understand
确认关系理解
interest that's the Philippians two word
这是腓立比人的两个词
look not out for your own interest but
看看不是为了你自己的兴趣而是
also the interests of others what is
还有别人的利益是什么
this part what are the other person's
这一部分是另一个人的
concerns and fears related to this issue
与此问题有关的担忧和担忧
understand their interests what seems to
了解他们的利益似乎是什么
be motivating them why are you concerned
激励他们你为什么担心
about this once you understand each
一旦你了解每一个，就这个
other's interests then brainstorm
其他人的兴趣然后是头脑风暴
creative solutions what are we gonna do
创意解决方案我们要做什么
about this we have a common problem
对此我们有一个共同的问题
that's attacking our relationship and
这是攻击我们的关系和
rather than sinfully responding by
而不是通过罪恶的回应
outwardly reacting like I have been or
像我一样或者向外反应
by internally seething like I have been
像我一样在内心沸腾
we need to brainstorm solutions to this
我们需要集体讨论解决方案
so let's work together as a team instead
所以让我们作为一个团队一起工作
of letting this issue be our enemy that
让这个问题成为我们的敌人
is tearing our relationship apart let's
正在撕裂我们的关系让我们分开
work together and then of all the things
共同努力，然后是所有事情
that you brainstorm evaluate your
你头脑风暴评估你的
options objectively and reasonably okay
选择客观，合理地好
we a brainstorm lots of ideas now what
我们现在集体讨论很多想法
are we gonna do and come up with a to-do
我们要做什么，想出一个待办事项
list to attack the problem the book the
列表来攻击这本书的问题
peacemaker has a whole chapter a Ken
和事佬有一整章肯
Sandy wrote that book and he has a whole
桑迪写了这本书，他有一个整体
chapter on how to use the pause
关于如何使用暂停的章节
principle if you're in negotiations with
原则上，如果你在谈判中
somebody like your spouse the other
另一个人喜欢你的配偶
another real practical book for families
另一本真实的家庭实用书
is called peacemaking for families and
被称为家庭和平的缔造和平
it goes through this pause principle
它经历了这个暂停原则
also transformation that was before
也是以前的转型
during real quickly develop an anthem
在真正的快速发展国歌
plan for how you'll deal with the times
计划你将如何应对时代
when you are tempted to anger I'll
当你被诱惑愤怒的时候我会
remind you again in the last session
在上一次会议中 再次提醒你
there was this thing called the anthem
有这个叫做国歌的东西
plan by John Piper
由John Piper策划
each one of the letters of the acronym
每个字母的首字母缩写词
stands for a different part of your plan
代表您计划的不同部分
so what are the things you need to avoid
那么你需要避免的是什么
what are the things you need to say no
有什么事你需要说不
to what are the things that you need to
什么是你需要 的东西
turn your mind toward Christ in the
把你的思想转向基督
moments of temptation what are the
诱惑的时刻是什么
things you need to enjoy about
你需要享受的东西
relationship with the Lord that are
与主是关系
legitimate pleasures and then how do you
合法的快乐然后你怎么样
need to move into useful activity toward
需要进入有用的活动
God and others learn to become
上帝和其他人学会成为
self-aware so that you know the moments
自我意识，让你知道时刻
and the types of situations where your
和你的情况类型
anger arises or your sinful
愤怒出现或你的罪恶
internalizing happens and develop a plan
内化发生并制定计划
ahead of time we call that a temptation
提前我们称之为诱惑
plan develop a plan to deal with it
计划制定计划来处理它
ahead of time and a lot of these have to
提前，很多这些必须
do with what are you doing during the
做什么你在做什么
time of temptation and you can go back
诱惑的时候，你可以回去
and review that then after if you fail
如果你失败了，那就回顾一下
let me make a comment about this and
让我这个注释，
especially if you're a person that's
特别是如果你是一个人的话
living with an angry person and they
与愤怒的人和他们 一起生活
determine that by God's grace they're
通过上帝的恩典确定他们是
gonna work on their anger issue or
要解决他们的愤怒问题或
issues remember progressive
问题记得进步
sanctification this is not about
成圣这是不是
perfection this is about increasing
完美这是关于增加
victory for those of you that may be
对你们这些可能的胜利
discouraged or your counsel leaves
气馁或你的律师离开
discouraged about anger and they've been
对愤怒感到气馁，他们一直都是
working on it have them think back where
努力让他们回想起去哪里
were you a year ago where were you two
你是一年前的两个人吗？
years ago how have you grown in your
几年前你是如何成长的？
relationship with the Lord and that can
与主的关系，那可以
be a very encouraging exercise for
是一个非常鼓舞人心的运动
someone who is so overwhelmed by
一个如此不堪重负的人
whatever the sin is in their life but if
无论生命中有什么罪， 但是如果
you're married to the angry spouse
你和愤怒的配偶结婚了
remember progressive sanctification so
记得渐进的成圣
if you fail I'm gonna just go through a
如果你失败了， 我会经历一个
whole bunch of those just so I could get
一大堆那些我才能得到
to this peacemaker ministries teaches
这个和平缔造者的部门教导
how do you make a confession to those
你是如何向那些人坦白的
that you've hurt address everyone
你伤害了每个人
involved
参与
so if it was public it becomes a public
所以，如果它是公开的，它就变成了公众
confession if you got angry in front of
如果你在面前生气，就认罪
your children and sinned against your
你的孩子和你的孩子犯了罪
spouse the children need to be involved
孩子需要参与的配偶
so that they know you got things
这样他们就知道你得到了东西
reconciled no excuses not well I
我没有找到任何借口
wouldn't have gotten angry if you
如果你不会生气
wouldn't have a void if button maybe
如果按钮可能没有空位
admit specifically I sinned against you
特别承认我犯了罪
by and name what the sin is it was
通过并说明它是什么罪
sinful for me to raise my fist at you it
我有罪，向你举起拳头
was sinful for me to hit that wall in
对我来说，打击那堵墙是有罪的
anger acknowledge the hurt it must have
愤怒承认它必须有的伤害
been very embarrassing for you when I
我这时候对你很尴尬
yelled at you in front of the children
在孩子们面前大吼大叫
you're trying to help the person know
你正试着帮助这个人
that you thought about this deeply
你深深地想到了这一点
enough so that they they know that you
足以让他们知道你了
are serious about this I realize accept
我很认真地接受这个
the consequences I realize that it may
后果我意识到它可能
feel like there's some barriers between
觉得两者之间存在一些障碍
us and I'm gonna work on tearing down
我们和我要努力拆除
those barriers I don't want there to be
我不希望那些障碍
barriers you're just trying to be
你只是试图成为障碍
realistic accept the consequences and
现实接受后果和
here's what I'm doing to change show
这是我正在做的改变节目
them your anthem plan here's what I'm
他们你的国歌计划就是我的意思
doing to change please help me please
做改变请帮帮我
pray for me will you forgive me not I'm
为我祈祷， 请原谅我，不是我
sorry
抱歉
but will you forgive me because when you
但是你会原谅我，因为当你
say will you forgive me you just turned
你会原谅我，你刚才转过身来
it into a transaction and now they have
它成为一个交易，现在他们有
to make a decision so that
做出决定，这样
reconciliation can take place then last
和解可以持续到最后
slide tell God and others what you plan
幻灯片告诉上帝和其他人你的计划
to do in the future and be on guard once
在将来做，并保持警惕一次
again and then just in conclusion a
再一次，然后只是结论一个
reminder look for decreasing frequency
提醒寻找降低频率
not perfection
不完美
you
您